MURARO SIMONE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

simone.muraro.95@amail.com

+39 3402785583

Padua (PD), Italy

29 years <u>old</u>

m www.linkedin.com/in/simone-muraro

simone-muraro.com





ABOUT ME

My main strength is my logical and analytical way of thinking. I'm a fast learner, adaptable to any situation and willing to put in the effort required to achieve my goals.

After two years of working as an application consultant, I decided to transition to a more technical and stimulating role. I dedicated several months to full-time learning of programming, and ultimately, I secured my current position at Wintech SPA.



IT SKILLS

JavaScript/TypeScript

MERN stack, Angular, React, Node, NestJS, Express, APIs, jQuery, EJS

HTML/CSS

Responsiveness, Bootstrap

Python

Langchain, Flask, web scraping, API, GUI (Tkinter)

Java

Java Spring, Spring Boot

Databases

SQLite, Oracle SQL, MongoDB, ChromaDB

Basic knowledge of Git and GitHub

Academic knowledge of MATLAB and R



OTHER SKILLS

Languages

Italian

Native language

English

В2

German

A2

Soft skills

- problem solving
- work organization
- > handling responsibilities
- > client relationship



WORK EXPERIENCE

Software developer Feb. 2024 - now Wintech SPA

Software developer. I am involved in a project aimed at integrating AI into business processes, and in the development of software for customers using BC language (proprietary language of Sistemi).

Company solution consultant May 2021 - Apr. 2023 Engineering SPA

Application specialist at the Hospital in Padua, with a role of responsibility and autonomy in the management of various activities, such as customer training and assistance, database maintenance and much more.



EDUCATION

Online courses Apr. 2023 - Nov. 2023 Udemy

I learnt programming independently. Check out my developer portfolio at <u>simone-muraro.com</u>

Master's degree in Bioengineering Sept. 2018 - Apr. 2021 Università degli Studi di Padova

Final mark: 101/110



CERTIFICATIONS

State Exam for Professional Information Engineer Dec. 2021 Università degli Studi di Padova